testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Uh
Hello.
testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
What is this?
Yeah.
testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
What is it?
Yeah.
testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Ah I pressed the wrong
What is it?
button.
Ah I pressed the wrong
Hey but why isn't it coming on? You can't hear?
No just wait a bit.
Hi.
Can you hear us?
We
have to go to the fansign now but
we wanted to do a live
even for a bit
so we came here.
Today
thank you.
Thank you so much.
It's our last broadcast today and we got 1st place so I feel so
really really
good about it.
We even got a triple crown.
Thank you Flover.
Thank you.
Flover
really.
Today
Are you going to eat Malatang and
Mala Xiang Guo
today?
That sounds delicious.
You should eat it today.
I had Tteokbokki today.
We all ate Tteokbokki together.
Yeah.
I achieved my dream today.
How was this promotion?
The visuals
Everyone was really so pretty this promotion.
I took a quick look.
Me too.
I think so too.
It feels like
the vibe was a bit different
from before.
Yeah compared to our past comebacks
we got a little more
mature.
But we've been saying
every day for about 5 years
that we got a little more mature.
But you know
it can't be helped when you look at our age.
Should I say
we got a bit more
beautiful?
Right.
It's kind of like
a feeling of
oh they are pretty.
The members are really beautiful.
Yeah in that sense
it's very beautiful.
That kind of feeling.
Flover.
How was it for you Flover?
Nakko's throat hurts today so she can't speak well.
Right.
If you go to the front the lighting
doesn't hit you.
Okay.
Speak for her.
Flover said it was so good
and congratulated us
on getting 1st place so much.
I'm so thankful.
Thank you.
Everyone is saying thank you so much right now
so I'm passing that on.
I should look at the comments a bit.
The Music Core
PD gifted this to us.
A hair tie?
Yeah.
Isn't it so cute?
It's cute.
I don't know is there a black one too
Should I put it on for you?
Put it on me.
Okay. Oh nice. Nice.
I'll read some comments now.
Ah you can log in through that.
Why?
Was the watermelon delicious?
But the watermelon is seriously so good.
It's really delicious.
Congrats so much on 1st place.
But there were so many Flovers crying today.
Seriously there was a Flover crying right in the front row
so when we won 1st place I suddenly
started crying too.
Before going on stage
and standing together right before we
went in
a Flover in the front told us
they'd make us get 1st place
and I felt so
choked up
about it.
Thank you.
Was everyone watching the live broadcast?
I'm sure Flovers
were watching it.
Was everyone watching the live broadcast?
I'm sure Flovers
were watching it.
But
some might have been working or at academies so they couldn't watch.
But we got a perfect score
on the live voting Flover.
Right.
But
we're really so thankful
and what's cute is
our staff members
also hurriedly
voted right before
it ended.
I voted too.
I spent 100 won.
Thank you thank you.
You did well.
Really
I mean it.
Although
this promotion is
over
I hope Flovers
keep listening to our song
and loving it.
We're charting right now.
Keep streaming.
Right it's going up so
please stream.
I listened to the album
all the way through with our manager on the way home yesterday.
We really
had a fun time.
all the way through with our manager on the way home yesterday.
But seriously
had a fun time.
whenever I listen to it
it's just so good
since the songs are great.
If the songs aren't that good
or if they get boring easily
it's hard to listen to them every day.
But I love them so much I listened to them this morning too.
Straight from track 1
all the way to track 10.
All ten tracks are so good
so I think
Flovers won't have a hard time
when streaming them.
The songs
are really worth
listening to.
Yeah.
Flover thank you
so much.
Really.
And we have a fansign soon
so to the Flovers coming
let's have fun together.
Ah so cute. I guess the Flovers
who came to the fansign
are all watching this together
right now.
Right they're all watching it together over there.
Make some noise if you're watching.
I feel like no one is making noise.
That's fine.
Ah and today at the
music show Music Core
about 400 people
came in right?
Yeah 400 people
came in and
the energy today
was seriously so good.
Right.
Stop spamming the chat.
Seriously
hey don't spam.
I can
see it all.
Yeah today
was the last broadcast so
I was
in a lot of pain.
Me too
I had some inflammation today.
Is it your left knee by any chance?
Yeah my left knee. Why?
Is there a move in our choreo
that causes it?
My left knee is weak too. Left knee.
Ah I'm on the younger side
so the unnies
are just like
wow.
But today was the last
broadcast so
I really didn't want to half-ass it.
You know what I mean right?
So I worked really hard.
We have to get going to the fansign now
so we'll leave.
Flover lastly
thank you once again
for giving us 1st place and thank you so much for being with us this promotion.
We exist because Flover exists.
Thank you.
Love you.
Let's make a big heart.
What is this?
One
two three.
Love you.
Bye.
Thank you.